ex.fm 2014-11-29

# Privacy Policy - Exfm

Extension Entertainment, Inc. (exfm) respects your privacy and recognizes the need for appropriate protection and management of your personal information, such as your name, email address and any other personally identifiable information you may provide to us. None of this information is currently required to utilize our service.

Exfm does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. We may use your personal information to contact you from time to time regarding updates to our policies, upgrades to our software, or other information that we feel may be of interest to you.

Exfm is a browser extension that works by saving links to mp3 files from web pages you visit while surfing. It then updates your browser extension with any new mp3 files to the pages you've already visited. Any mp3 file indexed is then available for playback in the extension, originating from the posted location. In addition to personal information you might voluntarily provide when you sign up, by the nature of its functionality, exfm software collects information regarding your Internet usage. Privacy controls include: deleting any individual item that you have visited and preventing the site from auto-updating songs into your music.

Exfm also has publicly available profiles where you may share music you love within the extension. This publicly available profile requires a valid email address.

Although we do not sell, trade or rent your information, we may release personal and/or non-personal information about you when you request us to do so. In addition, your information may also be accessed by exfm employees as necessary to provide customer support and troubleshoot problems.

We may also release personal and non-personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements, or to protect the rights of exfm or others. Information collected about you is protected in several ways. Access by you to your personal information if you sign up for an account is available through a password and unique user ID selected by you. Your password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone and change it often.

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

Your personal information resides on proprietary and secure servers on Amazon Web Services. Only selected exfm personnel and contracts have access to it via password. The Amazon Web Services facilities are subject to the terms and conditions of Amazon's Web Services [Licensing Agreement](http://aws.amazon.com/agreement/).

At any time, you may request to view or update the personal information that is associated with your account and stored by exfm. You may also request that we delete all personal and/or non-personal information that we have collected about you. We will promptly fulfill your request and provide you confirmation when the information has been deleted.

Because the Internet is constantly evolving, so are our policies. By agreeing to our terms of service, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as it may be amended from time to time. While we may send you a copy of any updates, we recommend that you check back to view the policy at this site from time to time.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or our information practices, please contact exfm at privacy@ex.fm.
